Guide to the Organization of Staff Analysts Records WAG.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files
  - Income Trends in New York State and New York City, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Job Vacancy Notices, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Labor at the Crossroads Awards Dinner, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Labor at the Crossroads Awards Dinner, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Labor-Management Health Insurance Policy Committee Meeting: Group Health, Inc. Renewal, May 17, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Labor-Management Quality of Work Life Committee Programs, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Labor Relations Order No. 81/1: Superseding PO 21/67 as amended, Classes of Positions, Aug 12, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Labor Relations Order No. 84/1: Amending LRO 81/1, Classes of Positions, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Labor Resource Center and Labor Media Watch, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Layoffs, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Legal Issues, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Legislation, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Legislation, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: "Workfare" materials and information, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Legislation: "Workfare" public hearing, Mar 11, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Claims for Expenses, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Claims for Expenses, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Claims for (Extraordinary) Expenses (Entertainment of AFSCME Officials), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Claims for (Extraordinary) Expenses, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Claims for Expenses, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Claims for (Extraordinary) Expenses, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Expense Battle Correspondence, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Time and Activity Sheets, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Time and Activity Sheets, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Time and Activity Sheets, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Leibowitz, Stuart (Stu): Time and Activity Sheets, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lists, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Lists: Alpha List of Passers, Apr 22, 1980-Apr 23, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Lists: Associate Staff List Movement by Agency, Jul 26, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Lists: Citywide Employees Breakdown for A Title by Agency, May 13, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Lists: Council of Personnel Examiners (COPE) Membership, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lists: Employee List by Agency for A Title - Citywide, Feb 24, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Lists: General, undated, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lists: Line Report for OSA Ballot, first the "A"s and second the "U" and "RT", Dec 19, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Lists: Members OSA/OSART, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Lists: Membership, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Lists: Organization of Staff Analysts (CBU 180), Feb 8, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Living Wage Bill, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Living Will, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Local 237, Teamsters: Campaign for Analysts, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Local 237, Teamsters: General, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Local 237, Teamsters: General, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Local 237, Teamsters: "Staff Analyst Bulletin", undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Local 237, Teamsters: "Staff Analyst Bulletin", 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Local Union Election Manual by AFSCME, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Made in USA: Mass Media Democracy Project, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Mailing Labels, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Mailings, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Mailings, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Mailings, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Mailings, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Mailings, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Mailings, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Mailings, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Mailings, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Mailings, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Mailings, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Mailings, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mailings: Reply to Aug. 23, 1993 letter re: FLSA Lawsuit (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mailings, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mailings, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mailings, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mailings, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mailings, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Mailings, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Mailings, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Mailings, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mailings, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Mailings, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Market Research, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Mayor's Personnel Order (MPO) 86/12, Aug 5, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Membership List: Listed by Department, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Membership Schedules, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Municipal Coalition Memorandum of Economic Agreement, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Municipal Credit Union, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Municipal Credit Union, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Municipal Credit Union, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Benefit Enhancements, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Budget Recommendations, [1999?] (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1992 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1993 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1997 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Conference of New York City Public Employee Unions, Nov 12, 1999-Nov 14, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Dues Increase, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Easy Rider Coalition, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Financial Statements, Jun 30, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): 457 Deferred Compensation Plan, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Committee Minutes, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): General Membership Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Intro 120, Mar 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Memorandum of Economic Agreement, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Privatization Committee, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Privatization Forum, Apr 18, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Proposed Budget, Jul 1, 1993-Jun 30, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Response to Mayor's Financial Plan, Mar 3, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Meeting, Jun 8, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Steering Committee Minutes, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Technical Health Sub-Committee, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Transitional Funding Program, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Narrow Banding, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Narrow Banding, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Narrow Banding, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Narrow Banding, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Narrow Banding, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Narrow Banding, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Negotiations, 1995-2000 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Negotiations: Citywide Agreement, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New York City Employee Benefits Program, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - New York City Employees' Retirement System, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - New York City Employees' Retirement System, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - New York City Employees' Retirement System Handbooks, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - New York City Fiscal and Economic Update, Dec 5, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - New York City Fiscal Update, Sep 16, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - New York City Fiscal Update, Apr 17, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - New York Metro Chapter: correspondence and related materials, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Constitution, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - No-Raiding Policy, Jul 24, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - No-Raiding Policy, Oct 24, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Non Dues Pay Positions, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Non-Managerial Employee Performance Evaluation Manual and Updates, 1980-1993 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Occupational Group: Position Descriptions, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): "About the OCB", undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "A", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Ba-Bl", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Bo-Bu", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "C", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "D", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "E", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "F", 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "G", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "H", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "I-J", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "K", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "L", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Ma-Mc", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Me-Mu", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "N", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "O", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "P-Q", 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Ra-Ri", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Ro-Ru", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Sa-Sh", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Si-Sz", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "T", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "V", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "W", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Administrative Staff Analyst (Levels I-III) Survey "Y-Z", 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Annual Report, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Annual Report, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Annual Report, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Case No. I-223-95 Systems Analyst (Post Hearing Brief), Jun 23, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 3-88, May 19, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 5-85, Jun 4, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 5-93, Feb 10, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 8-86, Jul 7, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 9-2001, Oct 9, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 12-79, Mar 28, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 14-86, Oct 16, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 17-91, Dec 17, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 20-82, Jun 10, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 21-84, Dec 26, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. 21-87, Oct 16, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Decision No. B-36-1999, Sep 1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Directory (Supplement) of New York City Public Employee Organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Directory of New York City Public Employee Organizations, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. A-6669-97 City of New York and OSA, Apr 17, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. RE-165-92 City of New York and OSA, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. RU-521-75, RU-533-75, RU-702-79, RU-707-79, RU-730-79 Staff Analyst Hearings/Interim Decision and Order, Nov 18, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. RU-521-75, RU-533-75, RU-702-79, RU-707-79, RU-730-79 Staff Analyst Hearings/Position Papers, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. RU-929-84 District Council 39, AFSCME, AFL-CIO and The city of New York, Decision and Order, Jul 14, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. RU-1160-94 OSA and the City of New York and Related Public Employees, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Docket No. Ru-1160-94 Administrative Staff Analysts, Levels I-III, Jan 7, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Impasse between OSA and City of New York and New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation pre-hearing brief, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Notice of Election and Eligible Voters in Human Resources Administration, Nov 7, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Staff Analyst Hearings, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Supervising Systems Analyst Survey "A-D", 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Supervising Systems Analyst Survey "E-J", 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Supervising Systems Analyst Survey "K-P", 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB): Supervising Systems Analyst Survey "R-W", 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Deferred Compensation Plan, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Employee Benefits Program, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Employee Benefits Program, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Employee Benefits Program - Long Term Care, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Employee Benefits Program - Long Term Care (Red), Aug 1998 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Health Benefits, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Office of Labor Relations: Municipal Coalition Memorandum of Economic Agreement, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Office of Management and Budget: Targeting Early Retirement, Nov 9, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Office of Municipal Labor Relations: Annual Leave for New Hires, Jun 20, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Office of Municipal Labor Relations: City Health Plan Documentation, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Office of Municipal Labor Relations: General, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Office of Municipal Labor Relations: RU 710-79, Aug 27, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Office of Payroll Administration: FICA Classifications, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Office of Payroll Administration: Implementing Automated Payroll Deductions, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Office of Personnel Administration: Outstanding Time Documents, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Office of Staff Resources Salary Administration Unit: Salary Chart, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - OSA and Related Titles (OSART): General, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - OSA and Related Titles (OSART): Meeting, Jan 14, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): Newsletter, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - OSA Retirees Club (OSARC): 10th Anniversary Celebration and Reunion, Jun 12, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Organizing Staff Analysts: General, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Organizing Titles, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Out-of-Title Work, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Overview of Civil Rights Laws Affecting Employment, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Parliamentary Procedure, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Pension: Articles, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Pension: Articles, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Pension Guide, May 1982 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Pension: Guide and Lecture prepared by Chuck Miller, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Pension Handbook: For Employees Represented by Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) Local 371, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Pension: Materials, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Pension: Materials, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Pension: Materials, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Pension: Materials and Articles, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Pension: Materials and Articles, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Pension: Materials and Articles, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Rules and Regulations of the City of New York, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Political Action Group: Attendance Lists, 1995-2000 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Political Action Group: Correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Predecessor Organizations: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Local 154-P, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Association of Personnel Examiners, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Council of Personnel Examiners (COPE), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 32)